{
    "id": "c8ba9366259e4de08384b793ea978658",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. on tip-toes, she reached for the mango.",
            "description": "She stood on tip-toes. She reached for the mango. We can combine these two sentences using the present participle.",
            "answers": [
                "Standing",
                "Stood",
                "Being stood"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acb85c41641342bcb8043ca4ece02685"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. hungry, the child ate the food greedily.",
            "description": "The child was hungry. The child ate the food greedily. We can combine these two sentences using being. Being hungry, the child ate the food greedily. ",
            "answers": [
                "Having",
                "Being",
                "Having been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be33e0ec2b3d4d379dc1d59fdb0533e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. his injury, he played exceptionally well.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. It is followed by an ing form or noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "665cf4ca3e0141fd83158eda089af804"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. injured his knee, he cannot walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Having",
                "Being",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dcd5562ff41a46dfbe44aa0f38e8de4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. himself in deep debt, he lost all hope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Finding",
                "Being",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4e3ec1a9396a4457b4c846dca1104223"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the event of such a thing ………………………, I will resign.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "happening",
                "to happen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee957858e71a405f9058c3c1b4829c8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He did not lose hope ……………………….. his repeated failures.",
            "description": "All of these are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "notwithstanding",
                "in spite of",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "dcab42bd200a4d939e2ba2548aa42b8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. taking the tablet, I didn’t get any relief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "31ce1b9a0ea9462f832109e39714f1ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. pity for the mouse, the seer turned it into a beautiful girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Feeling",
                "Being feeling",
                "Feel"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b0c0be3b14a54627802a713f42be79cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. tired, I lay down to sleep.",
            "description": "I was tired. I lay down to sleep. We can combine these two sentences using being. ",
            "answers": [
                "Being",
                "Having"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "85703bbf71b04f87b671a1241997e377"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. much blood, he struggled to stay awake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Having lost",
                "Being lost",
                "Having losing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c46bd51727ca40c887d960322a9b2369"
        },
        {
            "question": "God ………………………., we shall meet again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wills",
                "willing",
                "being willing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d81334dbe9884bf78c7f569b9b1790d4"
        }
    ]
}